well welcome to yet another Mastermind
with who is truly Professor Johanna
Sophia of johanna's raw foods and
coaching and the super happy body course
and the newly founded online
rossumlife.com rossumlifeglobal.com
um online university
um today we're talking about something
that has been kind of popping up from
all sides of society from all angles
from all avenues of political
convictions and thinkers and
um
and endless Warriors as opposed to
people who worry all the time
but there seems to be quite evidently
some truth to the fact that big changes
are happening in the world of money
and we have all heard about that the
physical money is supposed to vanish
that's why the title The Vanishing money
of this Mastermind
um and instead we will have I said
numbers and symbols and Q codes QR codes
um on our phones or other devices or
implanted in our hand or in our brain
um
if we submit to such alterations of our
physical body
um so that the entire monetary system
is planned to change and of course those
who who plan have particular agendas in
mind
and I wanted to look at
what actually has been and is money and
how does it impact our health and that
whole play between health and money and
money and health and how dependent our
health in the Western World in
particular no actually in the entire
world is on
the monetary schemes that are going on
everywhere because as the good old
saying goes money runs the world right
so money runs our health and how can we
evolve from the submission to that being
run by the powers that be and Empower
ourselves to get to Healing the last
Mastermind I did was called self-healing
for cheap it kind of went in the same
direction
but I did not much lay out the bigger
picture of what is happening with money
and what money is
um I think this
opportunity where this big change has
happened happening toward digitalization
to what everything being digital in
terms of what we have and what our
history is and what our degrees are and
how many kids we have and what our
ancestry is and how much money we make
and
what political persuasion we have
whether we are good citizens and fit
into the demands of the respective
powers that be and therefore can operate
more or less with that digital money
that can also be just wiped out
and that is not to say
that this is a new thing
and actually that's what I wanted to
point out many people are talking about
oh my God we've always had money and and
then it can suddenly be wiped out
the fact that money has always been
fictitious
is something that we're not really aware
of because we've been taught that money
is just the counter value for something
that is actually
that is actually in the bank or in the
gold or in the other value items that
are stored somewhere
welcome Joan say hello
we've just started
so I wanted to explore that a little bit
what money actually is and why it was
possible and how it was possible to take
over the ruling the ruling of the world
so why it got to the point that money
runs the world
of course originally an invention of
a piece of paper in ieou instead of gold
coins or other such
items that actually in and of themselves
had value or to represent that this
building or this
um
item
is now
not mine anymore but yours
um
shows us that of course the printing of
an IOU or a certificate of ownership is
also very very old and an old concept
and yet
it had never really extended to our
bodies
our health
and that is a new phenomenon of course
of the 20th century
that
the industries developed in such a
manner and some of you may be familiar
with the fact that a few large
industrialists sat together
in 1910
Rockefeller Rothschild melon Morgans
and a couple of others
sat together Carnegie I think was also
in that group
um
sat together and said okay we own all
this oil what can we do with it
and
the decision was we want to do
everything with it in fact at the time
these five six families owned 50 of the
world's wealth because they owned the
railroads and the oil Mining and the
coal mining and the of course the steel
companies Etc
and at that time
they figured well if we can make
materials like Plastics and the fresh
Plastics would evolve we can make
furniture Furnishings we can build
buildings we can build containers of all
kinds we can can we make food
and that did not quite work at the time
but can we make medicine yes
we can because we've developed poison
gases also on the basis of oil and gas
out of the ground
and we know that those
substances that we've created
you know the the first world war was
imminent
um
we can make medicine because we can have
these killer gases and killer substances
that we have developed that do not occur
like this in nature so and that is not
to say that they haven't been
poisons used as medicines beforehand
I learned not so long ago that
Mercury was used as a cure for Syphilis
or for other severe inflammatory
diseases Mercury
and arsenic so those substances that
occur naturally in the world that we can
find
had already been used as medicine in
the world so
we see at that time 110 115 years ago
the first concepts of the pharmaceutical
world what became the pharmaceutical
world of Medicine
the allopathic Avenue and they decided
at that time that all natural modalities
of healing would be eliminated
would be called hoaxes would be driven
out of town as snake oil
um fake
people and therefore the only acceptable
medicine to create Health would be made
out of this oil
now as if this were not enough
to
own the health industry
the next sought inevitably must be
that when you live in a
um money driven world we also call that
capitalism
um
then we want to have
control over as much sales as possible
right so we want to keep selling the
products that we're making we don't just
want to give somebody one little bottle
of medicine and after that they are
cured and never have to come back
because that's not a good business model
so at the same time the system develops
that
a
a lost a a healed a cured patient is a
lost customer so we have this concept as
of that period of time that as a doctor
if I am a doctor I will want to keep my
patients coming back regularly and have
more and different ailments and diseases
that I can prescribe medicines for and I
can service right it's like a car is not
supposed to be running for 50 years
without breaking down because there
would be no business in the car repair
and car servicing Industries so our
bodies have become this
product or our illnesses have become the
product that is necessary for the
medical industry to operate
and because
that has become the number one profit
making industry in the world why do I
know this
because in the
1990s and early 2000s until 2008
actually for 16 years I worked for an
international law firm and translated
lots and lots of documents and patents
and Deals and international
Communications
um
between
governments and corporations and
corporations by the office with each
other
and it often included statistics so the
number one profit making the highest
profit margin garnering industry was
already then the pharmaceutical industry
right next to or sometimes even above
weapons
weapons of course are the second
um and depending on the time period the
first and most profit
garnering
Industries in America
so
we've had this realization
if we so decided to have this
realization that
our health is driven by a profit making
industry
and that industry became the largest
industry on the planet so much so that
more and more disease has to be created
so that it can be serviced
and you get to a point where that
doesn't expand anymore
oh dear
our fifth booster is not being taken up
what now
I know that I'm going out on a on sin
ice here with these statements but it's
all just simple logic and just simple
fact right when an industry is based on
expansion and we must make more and more
money for our shareholders then that is
what drives us
and the mechanisms by which those monies
are earned are
driven by that
motives are designed to to feed those
motives
okay now we
um
we want to
look at what happened to the financial
industry because of this incredible
expansion and of course not just in the
health industry in the in the
in all Industries we have expanded to
such an extent that the planet cannot
hold for the expansion and
I should not forget that I also
translated lots and lots of documents
pertaining to derivatives and Futures
and the sales of debt and of course our
entire monetary system is based in debt
I think most people know that today that
money is
a death certificate right and when
somebody owns a lot of properties
somebody else must be in debt for the
same amount when somebody owns or has
has an asset two million dollars there
must be other people that are indebted
for two million dollars and they of
course it spreads over people so if we
want to increase this system again and
again and again we get into a deadlock
where the pyramid crumbles and we have
to crush it and start over
and we are so many people believe at one
of those points where we need to to
crash
and crush the existing situation
so that we can start over and that's how
the digital system gets its opportunity
to fill that new start
and of course my thought is as long as
we stay in the same system
this will always happen
and when you look back over time you see
that every decade there is a different
financial crash in the Western World
certainly
um
so but what does this all have to do
with health of course apart from the
fact that Health has become an industry
that is the second largest industry in
the U.S and in many Western countries
um
and
if we really do want to be healthy
because our money is
being reduced and there's going to be
less value in it so and of course if we
do not want to be chipped that may even
carry more
um punishment if you will in terms of
the monetary
[Music]
um
the the availability of money the the
assignment of of money
um so that we then
have even less ability to
look after ourselves in terms of staying
healthy so I want to talk about what we
can do to whether this whole storm and
get through it and possibly create more
awareness of how we can truly heal our
bodies and how we can truly actually
have a life with less dependency on that
whole system
um
so Health with little money or no money
is of course easily achievable if we
have access to Nature if we have access
to plant Foods
um
and that we have to be careful to set up
in such a manner that we have that
access whether we have our own backyard
whether we grow Sprouts or
little beets in our look at this these
are beet tops in our own window sills
or whether we
have to go to stores or whether we make
agreements with with Farmers with local
farmers organic farmers of course
um and see that we get supplies that are
not impacted by the monetary system
doing its thing until it rebalances now
do I think that that everybody will go
for this new system I think not I think
there's a large part of the population
that will say no
and therefore there is a great
opportunity to offer new ways of
doing
exchanges doing bartering or as you know
if they can print money I say why don't
we print our own money in the
communities we're in and some
communities of course have started that
why don't we create a system that we
want to have
and let me quickly still talk about
a couple of people I know who have done
so there's a village just Upstream from
me and on the Hudson that has developed
a currency I think they've even called
it a Hudson
um so you can have you can have your own
little printed paper money for that
Village and and certain
um stores and maybe a Mason and a
carpenter and a plumber Etc you know all
participate and already you have a
system of exchange that is independent
now there's lots of other issues that
come with such
new ways of doing things because it
still does not get you out of
taxes right every piece of land we own
um is taxed every piece of
uh
Earth or real estate we own is taxed and
that brings into question the whole
notion of ownership and how that should
be reconfigured in a future society that
would be less exploiting that would be
less
um
less greedy let's put it that way and
therefore would not have to crash once a
decade
so there's a lot happening at this
particular time and I wanted to make you
all aware
um
in terms of inventing new systems of
course my favorite new system is the
gradito
the thank you money that
um a German
um
a German
gentleman has
worked out over the last 20 years and
now there's thousands of people
exploring all the ways it can be
implemented and used it's called the
gradito
and
I would love to see if
using the internet as long as we can use
it freely
um two also create online communities
that do that that work with each other
and exchange with each other in new ways
now of course we all still have to live
in the existing world we all still have
to paint our mortgage our rent our
whatever we are we are
committed to our car our our fuel our
our electricity whichever we're using
right because we we if we want to stay
alive we have to function in the
existing system but that doesn't prevent
us from at the same time creating a new
system
and that works in the monetary system as
well as in the health system coming out
of the monetary system having one foot
in there we can still say but I am now
no longer the
Pawn of my medical practitioners I want
to actually take care of my own body I
want to actually learn to self-heal and
of course that is also where those of us
who have done that with our own
research and energy have done it with
our own body I myself
um
really learned how to do it better when
I had a stroke now
um almost 30 years no 20 years ago not
30 20 years ago I was 50 and
then switched to a
very high raw food diet high percentage
meaning 90 raw and I'm sorry my hair is
falling
apart and it's bothering so no whatever
um so yeah we can sometimes when we have
a very
dire situation
make that step into okay I don't need to
be dependent on the medical industry I
can do this for myself I can create a
lifestyle that creates a body that is
very healthy the last Mastermind I
talked a lot about how biology works on
planet Earth and how biology of course
Works in this here body in every body
and in every body's body
and therefore we
we can realize that we have that ability
and we can realize that we can learn
from others how to do that happily and
deliciously so when I say you know come
study with me then I know that you can
achieve something that is incredibly
successful
um although there are there are persons
for whom
it is difficult to give up the
dependency for whom it is difficult to
give up also the
the victim
mode
oh Society is doing this to me because I
am a woman because I am different
because I am and so forth there's lots
of reasons
why we can perceive ourselves as victims
and I I used to say with friends of mine
who you know I used to say with a smile
on my face yeah you just love your
diseases so much
there is an infatuation with this ah I
am so sick I have to take these 5 10 20
pills every day and see my doctor
regularly because oh I'm I have such bad
luck I am so sick you know or whatever
something happened to me or I did
something at one point and so forth so I
remained the victim stepping out of that
is very difficult for many people
and of course we all fall back into it
for moments in many situations
that happen to us
however healthy we are right
I mean for me the last time
I actually was down with a disease or
with a I call it exhaustion
flu
was after I traveled extensively
um and of course I don't do all the
the
um
the whatever requirements that they had
before they had just eased up on the
requirements so I I traveled to Europe
and it was just a very intense travel
and of course we're exposed to a lot of
stuff and I'm not just saying we're
exposed to shedding and
um and other people but we are also
exposed to enormous amounts of
electromagnetic fields and that is of
course the next level of Science and
understanding of science that everything
is electric or everything is energy
right so I turn that around and say okay
yes I am impacted and I didn't pay
enough attention of how much I'm
impacted because I was so busy doing so
many things outside of my personal body
and its concerns
that I did not Empower myself
sufficiently to build up my
electromagnetic field and my energy to
have this Shield or this broadcast that
I can actually create
and that is something else that I love
to teach and would love to help you with
that when we understand or begin to
understand you know there's no fully
understanding anything because there's
just
the more you know the more you know how
little you know
that kind of understanding but the more
we understand that we can have this
incredible power
to broadcast to understand if I put this
in my body it will be good if I put this
in my body well not so good if I do this
kind of breathing it will help my
circulation if I do this movement and if
I show up in this world with my mission
with my purpose it will be a very
different energetic field and it will
actually Propel me into that next era
where I can create
the new world the way I think it should
be as opposed to where I have to like
defend myself against all this onslaught
of terrible stuff
that
pose in and of itself of course again
turns us into a victim if I say oh my
God they're going to do this to us
they're going to do that to us that does
not Empower me if I say yeah I'm aware
they're trying to do this
however I am
stronger
I know how to deal or I will find out
how to deal that is my position it's not
that I know everything and that I can
everything but I will make
a very concerted effort to always learn
more as to how I can and can do more
and it starts right here with our body
so bringing it back home and very simple
we can learn
to be more self-sustaining
with our food and our
health
and I have a two-month course that I
teach learn to be more self-sustaining
and we can also learn to really really
grow into that purpose
and be among the people who are creating
a different
World a different societal structure a
different
exchange of value
a different understanding of ownership I
mean we've already understood that it's
not such a good idea to own people right
there was such a good explanation
so we believe in the free market system
which of course 200 years ago still
allowed
slavery right because that was a market
item are they humans to be traded and of
course we still have that with child
um
um trafficking in today's world
and somebody who said I don't think you
should do that
would interfere with the free market
system
eye popping yes so there are
new values have to be established new
well morals is to me a difficult word
because it's so often
ah so superficial right but this deep
morality that all humans are created
equal
all humans have equal value to the
existence on to the to the whole of
humanity to the planet
even if they're not contributing because
they may be
special needs or they may be
um non-productive in what others or in
comparison to what others can do so when
we get to that understanding or we move
toward that understanding
um then we also have an easier time to
move toward
nature is here
to feed us to heal us
to be the material to build with
to provide us with the inspiration for
creation for art
for
Beauty it's all here
if only
we got away from
the concept of
yeah but you can't have it because I own
it
so there's a lot to be learned and the
same is true for health
when we depend on the on the
currently called conventional system
we allow ourselves to be owned by it
because we are providing
the product
our diseases
so let us all step out of that modality
step out of the
um submission and the victim situation
and begin and use this opportunity where
the money is having this big transition
to say okay we are doing our own big
transition because some transition has
to happen because the money system is
collapsing the all the funds that are in
all the social uh funds whether it's
Social Security or Pension funds all
over Europe all over the US Etc and and
even banks are actually in default and
so deeply indebted that there's no way
we can get the
trillions and trillions of
dollars back from anywhere
even if we exploit
millions and millions of people and
children
um in the Congo and elsewhere to do for
pennies the stuff that we then sell for
thousands it is not going to make up for
the incredible debt that we have created
so just to put that out there in your
Consciousness you know this is a
wonderful moment to step into our power
and to say we don't need that system
anymore we can we are now wise enough we
are intelligent enough we are
understanding enough mature enough to
not need that competitive system but we
can enter into a contributory system we
can contribute to each other and he help
each other heal help each other have the
happiest fulfilled life that we all
desire so I'm not saying it's going to
be Utopia but but it can be pretty
awesome it can be pretty awesome when we
learn to self-heal and
collaborate with others who are on a
similar path
now
I have spoken long enough I would like
to hear
from my participants here
what resonated with you
and what maybe you thought something was
completely out of whack
um
please give me some thoughts
I know surely you have a lot to say
about this
and Ed what are your thoughts
and Joan I would love to hear your
thoughts
and Deborah who's probably listening
from afar
because she's no longer in front of her
camera
um
Thomas I
don't know which Thomas you are
um
if you don't want to speak
okay somebody was typing
okay okay Ed is not a bot
good to know egg
you have not transformed into a bot
sorry I'm very interested and appreciate
that you are doing this I didn't know
how this would be structured and timing
for me
please don't take offense I have to
leave because of an unexpected
Interruption and have to leave button
will really want the
recording
okay so the the text repeats itself it
seems or parts serif
yes um the recording will be on my
YouTube channel Johannes raw foods I
think yes
I have too many channels and things all
right yes so
if I'm not getting any
any questions
then I'm going to talk some more but you
know I never run out of words but I
would love your take I would love to
hear
what
what resonates with you what you think
um
oh
Joan is just texting me and says what
about using cash yes of course
unfortunately when Cash When the regular
cash gets banned or you're not gets
there's no nobody printing it anymore
then you're still in the situation
because the cash of course is run by the
major Banks and
um
yeah I just heard another talk again
that the World Bank is has gone
completely awry
and the bank of all banks
I think Catherine Austin Fitz was
talking about it yes
um
is fully aware that
the system as it is cannot hold so since
even regular cash is part of that same
system you still have to get the cash
from somewhere out of the bank out of
the ATM machine or from somebody else
who happens to have some cash under
their mattress but that's not going to
suffice to buy a house or to Etc so we
have to think
uh new ways of doing things and I think
it's a wonderful opportunity I don't
know whether it will happen yet in fact
I think
um the crash might not even be as severe
as is announced however a lot of people
especially the middle class will get a
lot poorer because we're the ones where
it's easy to siphon off money
and I mean I just heard on on another
broadcast I think it was unredacted
um that it already is happening that
people are missing money from their bank
accounts so if you want to go and take
out some cash to go and have some legal
tender in cash and there isn't any
available
ironically it was the same day that I
went to an ATM machine to put money in
but the ATM just was not working now
that maybe Coincidence of course as all
of it but it was ironic that it was the
same day that I was just hearing this
from all over the Western world that
people have been unable to take money
out of
um their bank account or realize there
was less in their account than they knew
to be there
yesterday or a week ago so
um there are already these things are
happening and credit cards are being cut
in terms of their limits that already
happened two years ago or it started
um so
of course
it will be eased in in various ways and
excuses will be had in various ways so I
was just saying let's work together in a
manner that has a foot in both worlds
where we know how the old system runs
and we say at the same time we're
building a new system so that we can
then switch over if and when this one
crashes completely it could be that it
doesn't that it just crashes a little
bit and comes back and has another run
at it for another couple of hundred
years that is very possible in my
understanding
and yet
so many people around the globe are now
saying
this is just not right because so many
more people are aware
especially since what we have lived
through the last three years now almost
and of course those three years also had
a lot to do with the fact that money was
running out and a crash was imminent and
putting people out of work and closing
their shops Etc created a different
Financial landscape globally
so when we're aware of all of that those
are all Stepping Stones toward the new
system and Stepping Stones Out of the
old system which is about to totally
fail
yeah
um so cash yes as long as we still have
some it's a good idea to use some
and at the same time
create systems or join systems where
people are trying something new and it's
you know it's not going to be the
perfect thing but we can start we can
start doing things in a different way
same as we're starting to do Health in a
different way right same as we're
realizing that the veggie juices and
veggie smoothies and
um so many very simple modalities you
know eating Sprout salads that where the
sprouts grow on our own windowsills
um if we don't have a gardener of course
if we do have a garden you know planting
some simple crops
um like you know I can only claim that I
planted
a sweet potato which grew a whole huge
patch of sweet potato leaves that are
very delicious in salads and smoothies
so and I want to do more of that in the
future of course
yeah
um
everybody with more awareness can do
more and I'm happy to teach all kinds of
modalities to self-heal
without
the traditional system
and sometimes you know we've already
gone through the traditional system like
a client of mine who had just had had
cancer and a hysterectomy and then came
and still the body is so capable of
rebuilding health and who's now you know
climbing mountains again and very
happily healthily living where if she
had continued on the same system path
it would have been over in a couple of
years so
even after some severe
impact that we've suffered from the
regular system
um for the lack of healing
through the modalities offered in the
regular system
um
we can still bring our biology back
that's the beautiful thing of of biology
on planet Earth and that is not to say
that we can live 500 years but we can
certainly live the 120 that we should
live happily healthily walking standing
talking breathing hearing smelling and
seeing and all the modalities that we
love to enjoy
as and that we call a good life right so
yes
um
to round up the the cash discussion yes
absolutely use cash wherever you can
um because it avoids
total grip of the the QR codes
over everything
yeah however like I said
we cannot stop
the fact that the banks are
bankrupt
um
we can't even if we use all the cash we
want we can't turn that around
yeah so it's going to be interesting
to see how much impact we can have
but of course every person counts and
every person counts toward creating a
new system
simply by saying okay no I'm not going
to take this chemotherapy I'm going to
heal myself I'm not going to take this
whatever medicine that I'm told I need
to take for the rest of my life for
diabetes because I'm going to heal
myself or I'm going to work with people
like Johanna who can actually help me
get out of the chronic disease that is
supposed to be chronic but that is
totally reversible
so that's that's my mission and finding
that opportunity in a crisis situation
is always what happens change happens
because of crises and because of the old
system loosening and and faltering and a
new system can arise from it so
I think that's the way the cookie
crumbles
because life Works in cycles and you
know there are lots of philosophical
explanations as to why but the more we
are aware the more we can
find our new past so join
join me join Johannes raw foods contact
with me contact everybody in your
neighborhood in your Regional area who
has to do something with organic growing
with alter alternative healing
modalities
um
and
yeah make sure that you don't fall for
the roses and there will be more ruses
Catherine Austin Fitz was talking about
the mind control
levels that propaganda has gotten to
yeah so you know all of that is going on
but the people who are trying to do mind
control have themselves a very
vulnerable mind too so we forget that
they're just humans and often not more
intelligent often less intelligent than
you and I so therefore
again
empowering ourselves
and doing
what we consider the next level of
living
is
what makes the old system obsolete
all right
tan I have one more final question
no
I'm not seeing anything in the chat
hello Joanna yes surely yes are you
encountered any
osteoporosis now
I found out that
taking helps him
perhaps it's not good for you I mean
calcium too and then well you perhaps
have gotten off of all Dairy I gave up
all berries 70 years ago
and
perhaps I tried myself
oh
steoporosis
yeah well osteoporosis has to do with
calcium but also with hormones yes
hormones and I was put on thyroid
yes so there you there you go
unfortunately and again because I worked
at the law firm I came across a lawsuit
that was filed by people who were given
hormone replacement drugs for whatever
reason whether it was thyroid or whether
it was
um
menopause
Etc and the lawsuit was that they filed
because they had as side effect
osteoporosis and other degenerative
bone-in tooth tissue issues
so
um so yes it's it's very real that
especially hormone replacement
um
medications as they may be called
um are actually destructive to the bone
structure and in our human body
um and and skin and all of the other
um
soft tissues as they are all called are
also affected
um
what you can do however is to
you can increase your leafy Green Plus
omega-3 intake so
um and I want to refer to Dr Brook
goldner here who does a wonderful
program
um using cruciferous greens
as the main part in a smoothie and then
you add a little bit of fruit to your
liking
bananas mangoes pineapple papaya
whichever you know you please berries
are very good of course
um and a couple of spoons of flax seeds
or chia seeds of course your smoothie
gets kind of thick but you get all the
fiber and you get all the calcium and
your body can create healthy cell tissue
because of the Omega-3s and that's what
I talked about a lot last time last
Mastermind and please everybody go back
to that if you want to hear more about
that
cell reproduction
requires especially essential fatty
acids and especially Omega-3s and of
course if we were eating watermelon with
their seeds in them and and all the
fruits you know including the seeds we
would have plenty but we take out the
seeds or we grow the plants so that they
don't produce seeds for example grapes
and and all the citrus fruits right
so we're missing those elements
um that's what I would say for
osteoporosis again you know very high
green and then of course breathing and
the right exercises so that our body is
trained to be more upright I you know I
have a crooked back and and I have a lot
of issues but they're not issues because
I'm fine with my body I love my body I
just make sure that I strengthen it all
the time and strengthening the um the
back in particular to be upright allows
the organs to function better allows the
organs to distribute all the nutrients
better and therefore again helps your
bone tissue to
to even get the nutrients that you may
be putting into your mouth but that are
not getting there because of not enough
movement or breathing oxygen
disbursements all over the body
um but yeah I'd I'd love to talk to you
about that
um separately surely if you want
did did somebody did somebody tell you
you had osteoporosis
well I finally had a steps that a dexa
scan
and I've been eating for 70 years
and perseverance can be bad for the
thyroid
I've done that research
yeah and also uh some types of beet
greens and beets
oxalates I've done this research well
that's a new fad you know it's just like
um
that is bad you know there are certain
faceted up at the new thing is oxalates
are bad for you and I I don't know I get
a little frustrated with these you know
um yes you need to drink your glass of
milk to get the calcium it's one of
those you know the the milk and the
calcium and the milk is good for the
calf and the cow you to become a cow
rather or or a steer a bull
um
and the same is true for the oxalates
you know the oxalates that that come in
organic good food
are not going to be a problem for your
system if all the other parts of your
life are in place and you want to get to
110 at least surely because you are
beautiful and strong and you know
I know you will so
for for
you it is much more important to do the
breathing and again I recommend
the Wim Hof breathing method but we can
like I said we can talk about this
separately
so that the distribution throughout your
body happens and of course you know the
movement I don't know what kind of
movement
um exercises you do
so I went to the shop with pesticides
when I was a child yes
and became paralyzed so that I had I was
told I would never run or walk again
and had to raise
yeah well I I made up my mind I am going
to run and I did that but of course at
that time I didn't have the best food
either because it was during the
Depression
yes and and that that again that proves
that it's all possible
and I need the food and to change your
food in heaven well
I uh perhaps
all that raw food had
can be difficult for a lot of people
because they too fast
yeah I think that's all ultimately
irrelevant because uh
you know like Brian Clement says Dr
Brian Clement
11 million species on the planet all eat
raw food many of them swallowed the
stuff whole and the stomach breaks it
down
and we are the only ones that don't know
how to feed ourselves right so
and it could be so simple it's it's
doctor did you remember Dr Fletcher you
said you have to have 32 shoes yeah but
again that's that's yet another fad you
know we no nobody has time to do 32
chews that's ridiculous no animal has
time to do that other than than the um
the ruminators who actually you know
bring food back up from the stomach and
then re-choo it but we don't in fact we
consider it not so healthy when we have
reflux
it's not a pleasant thing for us so no
we're not ruminators we do not need to
chew 33 times per byte you know I mean
there's just so many Concepts out there
that that don't make any sense because
uh somebody uh invented them and made a
splash with them and invented or
whatever a medication or wrote a book
about it or uh yeah I I just don't
go for those well if we go to if we just
swallow it as you get older you can
choke so you need to chew it some to get
the have the enzymes like the proper
enzymes in your mouth well you
etc etc etc and of course you know if
you don't have perfect teeth you have
machines you have knives you have Forks
you have you know you have all sorts of
things to help you break stuff down
um that's what we do when we make
smoothies right we use basically a knife
to chop the stuff into very very small
parts and
to me that all works you know that's why
we are humans we are creative we can do
we can of course also just go out and
eat the whole apple and the whole
whatever mango papaya Etc and live off
that or pull the roots out of the ground
and chew them like that but that would
take most of our day to come up with the
foods that would be necessary for our
maintenance and and growth
and Longevity so yeah we have to find
creative ways and of course we also love
flavors and we love beauty we we make
beautiful dishes we make them look
pretty
Etc so all of the above
is is what makes us humans creativity is
what makes us humans
and also
right one using our all of our senses to
appreciate the food exactly making our
senses appreciate the food and that's
your taste your vision your smell right
yes and sometimes also when you eat food
with your hands depending on what it is
you know when we eat of course fruit and
hold it in our hands that too is a is a
wonderful experience or you know many
cultures eat with their hands and I've
had the pleasure of partaking in so
those modalities it's a beautiful
ceremonial experience so
so yes surely I'm happy to have a
separate conversation with you
especially regarding osteoporosis
because yes it is a very important issue
ironically mostly in the western world
and um has of course its causes but it
also is miraculous how we can overcome
these issues
from diabetes to osteoporosis via
arthritis via uh
all the other issues cancers allergies
etc etc migraines
um backaches belly aches IBS Etc
all of them can be reversed and
I'm not saying that you're going to be
the strongest you know because it's not
about competition it's about making this
body you have work wonderfully for what
you need and and want to do it right
against yourself to Major yourself
not
saying that you are better than women
I mean just compare yourself as you move
forward with the steps
yeah all right well you may know that my
Mantra is we need to transition from
competition to contribution in all of
society and that again you know is the
the changeover of the monetary system
and the change over of our
healing ourselves
go hand in hand with that concept
transitioning from competition to
contribution in all of life
and maybe I can I can end it here
and it will be interesting to see how
the monetary system The Vanishing money
develops and what we come up with to
use the moment to birth New Concepts and
new ways of being with each other and
being with our body with our health
yes I think you should be writing an
article for a book
about
about your new system of power free
yes
I I agree
and
and it's in the works as are so many
other things first I I want to
help more people individually and create
the University or get the university to
open
and lots of love to all of you guys I it
has been my pleasure having you here and
let me know later in the comments please
what you think about what's being
discussed here and how you think you can
participate as well
so
now you said ciao everybody bye bye bye
talk to you later
sweeties
everybody in the world
and they like to give uh the prizes the
Nobel prizes to every contribution
maybe you'll receive a Nobel Prize Ah
that's not my goal no no oh